(Leonard:)That must be him.
SHELDON:
Oh, of course.
(Sheldon:)An nondescript,
white panel van.
(Sheldon:)You may be familiar with
it from the sentence:
"Their bodies were found in a
nondescript, white panel van"
(doors close)
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Stuart:)What's up?
(Leonard:)Uh, I'm Leonard.
(Leonard:)This is my friend...
I'm Skippy.
(Sheldon:)Skippy Cavanaugh.
(Howard:)Great.
(Man:)You got the cash?
(Leonard:)Uh, yeah, uh,
right here.
(Sheldon:)Wait, hold on, hold on.
(Sheldon:)How do we know
that you're not gonna
(Sheldon:)take the money
and drive away?
(Leonard:)What ya doing, Skippy?
(Sheldon:)Exactly what 1970s television
crime dramas have taught us.
(Sheldon:)You give us the helium first.
(Man:)Oh, how do I know
you're not gonna
(Man:)drive away without paying me?
(Sheldon:)Guess I'm not the only one
(Sheldon:)who watches '70s television
crime dramas.
(Leonard:)Look, you can trust us.
(Leonard:)We're respected scientists.
(Sheldon:)Well, he is.
(Sheldon:)I'm a wedding planner,